<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experience on Joshua Jebaraj</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experience on Joshua Jebaraj</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One year at we45</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/we45/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/we45/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a year since I started working at &lt;a href=&#34;https://we45.com/&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;we45&lt;/a&gt;. In this blog, I am gonna share my working experience at we45&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;opportunity&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Opportunity&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#opportunity&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been following we45 since my college days when I started to explore DevSecOps. During my final year when I started looking for a job, I reached out to Abhay and ask him whether there are any openings in we45, to my luck, there are some openings and I applied for the same.&#xA;Before starting the Interview I reached out to &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/abhaybhargav&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Abhay&lt;/a&gt; and I asked a bunch of questions regarding the company like work culture, mentorship, work pressure, etc. Abhay was kind enough to answer all the questions and after I was satisfied with the answer , the initial interview was set up. Initially, I was a little bit anxious because I don’t what they were gonna ask during the Interview. The folks at the Interview made sure that I was comfortable and it was more like a conversation. We discussed what I learned so far and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://joshuajebaraj.com/#projects&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;projects&lt;/a&gt; that I have worked on so far. After clearing the Interview I joined the we45 in June 2021&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Internship Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/intern-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/intern-experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-internship-experience-at-atlan&#34;&gt;&#xA;  My Internship experience at Atlan&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#my-internship-experience-at-atlan&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello friends in this blog I am gonna share my Internship experience at &lt;a href=&#34;https://atlan.com/&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Atlan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-opportunity&#34;&gt;&#xA;  The Opportunity&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#the-opportunity&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last May when I started looking out for the internship Initially I was struggling to get the roles that I am looking for But unfortunately, not many companies offer the role that I am looking for I was worried that I won&amp;rsquo;t find the role that I am looking On a fine night when I searching for the internship that came across DevOps Internship opening at Atlan After going through the company blog I found below the line in their company website &lt;strong&gt;Our interns work with us, not for us&lt;/strong&gt;. Without any second thought, I immediately applied for the internship (I applied at 3 am xD). After applying for the Internship, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hear back for a while so I thought I didn&amp;rsquo;t get selected for the next round. After 2 weeks I got the mail stating that I am selected for the second round . In the second round, they gave me a medium-level challenge based on the role that I applied for after completing the challenge I got selected for the Technical round. I was very nervous during the round because I thought they gonna ask me about Data Structures and System Design (Which I never Like Personally xD).To my surprise, the questions revolved around the task that I performed during the last round, rather than focusing on the tools and knowledge they asked me about my approach. After the technical Screening I was selected for hr round I was very nervous because I am not sure what they will be asked in the interview because I never faced such type of interview in my life honest Like the last round this round was also very surprised to me most of the questions are revolved around my past life and current plan and future goals, throughout the hiring process the team make sure that I am comfortable during the interview and makes the process smooth and clear&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Baby Steps in DevSecOps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cdp-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cdp-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone In this blog I m gonna explain my baby steps into the DevSecOps During my last Internship at Practical DevSecOps I got an opportunity to take the CDP exam  I have learned a lot from the course In this Blog I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share my experience of my first Certification&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-opportunity&#34;&gt;&#xA;  The Opportunity&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#the-opportunity&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While exploring DevSecOps I came across a course on DevSecOps from the Practical DevSecOps I was stunned on seeing the course syllabus but was sad on seeing the course fee So I pinged Imran if he can offer me a discount or something. Instead of a discount, Imran told me we are looking for interns. Will I be interested in working with him? Without a second thought, I said yes, after which we had a few calls regarding my internship. Imran gave me a hiring challenge which I completed after which I was hired as an intern at Practical-DevSecOps. My day to day role at the company was to create the content and labs for the free docker security course. I like his effort to contribute to the community and got to learn many things from Imran like how to interact with people, how to get your work done. Apart from Imran, we have Ifran, Nadira, Yuga, and Ali who became good friends of mine. Even Though We work from different parts of the world I still feel like a family. I also got a chance to interact with many amazing people one of them is Ishaq, who became good friends of mine who helps me with technical doubts and reviewing my contents and posts(including this blog post). I also met other few good people on the Slack channel who helped to clarify my doubts . After completing my 6 months of internship Imran offered me to take the course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
